Elisabeth Myers

IT Support Specialist

Vancouver, WA - Email me on Indeed: indeed.com/r/Elisabeth-Myers/1b2e6d8ab04df2b3

Experienced IT professional with a strong commitment to customer service. Proficient in support of a wide variety of hardware and software applications with excellent troubleshooting and problem solving skills.

WORK EXPERIENCE

IT Support Specialist

City of Odessa - Odessa, TX -

September 2014 to March 2017

Provided technical support and customer service to all city employees.

Provided high-volume installation, repair, and deployment of user PC's and other hardware accessories.

Installed and performed necessary troubleshooting for a wide variety of different software applications.

Created documentation on issue resolution and software installation/support.

Trained users on necessary computer skills.

IT Applications Intern

Concho Resources, Inc. - Midland, TX -

May 2014 to August 2014

Developed an in-house solution to report generation and management using SQL in a Microsoft Access database.

Assisted Help Desk personnel with general IT services such as troubleshooting user issues, installing new software, and deploying new PC's.

Engineering Intern

John Crane Production Solutions - Midland, TX -

May 2012 to August 2013

Created three dimensional models of down-hole well structures using Solid Edge modeling software.

Wrote reports on well failure analysis with assistance of senior engineer.

Managed MS Access inventory database, performing indexing and duplicate removal.

EDUCATION

Bachelor's of Science in Computer Science

University of Texas - Odessa, TX

May 2014 to August 2014

SKILLS

Windows (XP through 10) (5 years), macOS (2 years), Unix/Linux (3 years), Networking (3 years), Hardware (PC's, printers, scanners, routers, switches, etc.) (5 years), Databases (MS Access, Oracle, MySQL) (4 years), Microsoft Office Suite (Access, Excel, Word, etc.) (5 years), Google Apps Suite (Calendar, Docs, Drive, Gmail/Inbox, etc.) (5 years)